<use-cases xmlns="http://technodrom.scravy.de/2010/use-case">
	<category>Public listings</category>

	<use-case>
		<title>A User displays list of lectures</title>

		<actor>Any user (anonymous &amp; logged in)</actor>
		<pre>The system is running.</pre>

		<ev>User clicks on a link "lectures".</ev>
		<ev>
			An alphabetically sorted list of all lectures is shown.
			<or>If too many lectures were to be shown, a multi-page is generated.
			</or>
			<or>If no lectures match the given filters (or there are none), a
				message like "no lectures match the given filters" is shown.</or>
			<or>The user may equally well stop here.</or>
		</ev>
		<ev>
			Using a form on that page, a lecturer can be searched or the current
			view narrowed (filtered).
			<or>A preset filter may be selected: "Display lectures recommended
				for my Year" (if the user is logged in). This should only display
				courses which are available (i.e. there are Course Instances in the
				running Academic Term) and subject of "recommendedForYear" with the
				Year of the currently logged in user.</or>
			<or>A preset filter may be selected: "Display lectures at my home
				institute only" (if the user is logged in).</or>
		</ev>
		<ev>The filter-form is submitted.</ev>

		<success>A page displaying an alphabetically sorted list, grouped by
			the first letter, is displayed.</success>
		<post>-</post>

		<q>Is the information about the current year of a student stored
			somewhere?</q>
		<q>Is the information about a "home institute" stored somewhere?</q>
	</use-case>

	<use-case>
		<title>Detail view for a lecture</title>
		<scope>GUI</scope>
		<actor>Any user</actor>
		<pre>The system is running and the user is logged in.</pre>
		<post>The system is still running and the user is still logged in.
		</post>
		<success>A page displaying information about a lecture is shown. This
			includes which Course Element Instances happen when &amp; where, who
			is the main lecturer, and Course Attributes. If the currently logged
			in user has sufficient rights, links for editing/deleting the
			currently shown resource may be displayed, too.</success>
		<ev>User opens the user panel.</ev>
		<ev>User enters the name of a lecturer.</ev>
		<ev>User clicks on submit.</ev>
		<ev>GUI displays a link to the lecturer.</ev>
		<ev>User clicks on the link.</ev>
		<ev>GUI requests user data from the database.</ev>
		<ev>GUI displays the lecturer data.</ev>
	</use-case>

	<use-case>
		<title>Anonymous user displays list of lecturers</title>

		<actor>Any user (anonymous &amp; logged in)</actor>
		<pre>The system is running.</pre>

		<ev>User clicks on a link "people".</ev>
		<ev>
			An alphabetically sorted list of all lecturers is shown.
			<or>If no lecturers match the given filters (or there are none), a
				message like "no data set matches the given filters" is shown.</or>
			<or>If too many lecturers were to be shown, a multi-page is
				generated.</or>
			<or>The user may equally well stop here.</or>
		</ev>
		<ev>Using a form on that page, a lecturer can be searched or the
			current view narrowed (filtered), e.g. "view only lecturers from the
			institute for computer science".</ev>
		<ev>The filter-form is submitted.</ev>

		<success>A page displaying an alphabetically sorted list, grouped by
			the first letter, is displayed.</success>
		<post>-</post>
	</use-case>

</use-cases>
